

Ella Walton

Receptionist

3620 Ettlehorn Street, San Francisco, CA 94016, United States (530)732-2544 <u>hw12@gmail.com</u>

Skills Excelient Communication Skills Multitasking Skills Office Technology Skills Scheduling Skills Bookkeeping Skills Customer Service Skills Languages Italian French Spanish

Profile

Hardworking and experienced Receptionist with several years of experience serving as a supportive and integral employee in high volume client settings. Experienced in creating schedules, making appointments, selling products, and providing clients with optimal customer service. Bringing forth the ability to manage front desk settings with poise and grace, in addition to managing a variety of administrative duties. Eager to join a new team of people, and assist them as a dedicated and passionate Receptionist.

Employment History

Receptionist, Alfred Young Design, San Francisco

November 2014 - August 2019

- Greeted clients and provided them with information and superior service.
- Handled calls, collected personal information, and managed schedules.
- Maintained accurate client records and provided lead designers with excellent assistance.
- Managed the office database, mail, payroll distribution, and the physical setting of the front office.

Receptionist, Little Star Day Spa, Los Angeles

June 2003 - October 2014

- Answered phone calls, greeted clients, and handled all front desk responsibilities.
- Decorated the front reception area, contributing to the welcoming and peaceful environment of the spa.
- Handled spa orders, mail, and some accounting responsibilities.
- Provided clients and prospective clients with information regarding services, spa technology, and products offered.

Education

Associate of Communications, Pierce College, Los Angeles August 2003 — May 2005

High School Diploma, Maria Regina High School, Sherman Oaks September 1999 – June 2003